[Music]
come
out oh hallelujah
[Music]
god
hold
[Music]
my hold
the hold the
[Music]
Go
i want
you away
i
[Music]
want think before you use a jutsu or
else your opponent might use it against
you
oh and also if the bait is obvious don't
take it
a ninja must see through deception i get
it
i'm telling you this because you don't
get it you think you get it which is not
the same as actually getting it get it
this is my chance he finally dropped his
guard
won't you ever learn
he just got blasted by Shuriken are you
out of your mind Sasuke you went too
[Music]
far another substitution jutsu and now
he knows where I'm hiding got to move
fast
i thought he lowered his guard but he
did that on purpose and I fell for it so
that's where he is
[Music]
sasuke where'd you go don't tell me
Kakashi since I found
you no he can't capture my Sasuke i
won't let him
he didn't hear me i'm safe sakura behind
you huh
a ninja must see through deception yeah
yeah how am I supposed to do
that well I'm sure not falling for any
more of his
traps i fell for it again
you failed kakashi's final decision
oh
my someone there i think I felt
something what was it what's going on
sakura sasuke
sakura help me please help me
[Music]
i think I overdid it a bit but she's got
to learn to see through these things h
sounded like Sakura shinobi battle skill
number two the illusion jutsu sakura
studied it in class but she still
couldn't see it
coming kenjutsu it's just simple mind
control i'm not surprised he caught
Sakura with it
but I'm not like Sakura and
Naruto say that after you get one of
these bells my Sasuke
[Music]
there's no point using normal
attacks a trap
what this kid
He's fierce i won't be able to read Make
Out Paradise
now what what
happened sasuke I saw him he was on the
verge of
No sasuke no you've got to survive
please where are you
[Music]
huh hey what are those things down
there i know what those things are those
are box
lunches oh a ninja must see through
deception
well you are different from the other
two i'll grant you that
horse tiger fire style fireball jutsu
what genine can't do fire jutsu takes
too much chakra there's no way
[Music]
where did he go behind me
above where
i'm where you least expect me
right under your feet earth style head
hunter jutsu
can't move huh that was njutsu the third
shinobi battle skill you have talent and
you were right you are different from
the others but different isn't always
better they say the nail that sticks up
is the one that gets hammered
down oh
great sensei told us that if we don't
get a bell then we don't get any lunch
but if I eat my lunch now then there's
nothing he can do it's chow time hi
there
i was just joking sensei nice try
he's stronger than I am i can't get
around that
[Music]
sakura's just a hand without a body and
he's talking
and that's my partner
[Music]
sasuke you're okay hey cut it out let go
let go
i've got to get a bell before lunch that
doesn't leave much time
sasuke you're still trying to get one of
those bells a while ago I touched one
next time I'll get one
that is really great i can't believe you
did that you're amazing i can't believe
it he touched one of the bails i'll
never get my hands on one of those
things which means Sasuke will pass and
I won't and we'll be separated forever
no no no no no uh it's almost lunch
there's not really enough time left so
maybe we should just give up and then
try again next year
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm the only one who can destroy that
person
what who you mean the sensei
that day I was crying
when were you crying
it was my
What what happened to you i am an
avenger that means I must be stronger
than my prey i need this training
there's no time for setbacks
[Music]
i'm going to restore my clan and destroy
a certain someone
i wasted too much time
sasuke
uh-oh stomach's growling huh that's too
bad oh by the way about this exercise
well I've decided I won't send any of
you back to the academy
what i passed all I did was faint and
fall over do you get points for that
loved ones out cha cha cha
then then that means all three of us I
mean all three of us yes all three of
you are being dropped from the program
permanently
unbelievable kakashi has never passed a
single student he fails all of them irua
this group is young even I cannot say if
it is good for them to face the rigors
and dangers of ninja life however
Kakashi was correct about all those he
failed
drop us from the program that means we
can never become ninja you said if we
couldn't take the bells we'd be sent
back to the academy you can't just
change your mind and kick us out why
would you do that because you don't
think like ninja you think like little
kids like brats
sasuke
you think it's all about you
let go of Sasuke you can't step on him
like he's some bug
you don't know what it means to be a
ninja you think it's a game huh
[Music]
why do you think we put you on squads
did you consider that question for one
moment i don't know what you mean i mean
you never realized what this exercise is
all about not even close what it's about
yes that's what determines whether you
pass or fail
but that's I mean I wanted to ask you
about that from the beginning
use your head three people on a squad
why do you think we would do that
[Music]
how are we supposed to know why you
picked three people we didn't make the
rules it's so basic teamwork
just working together is that what you
mean that's what I mean it's too late
now but if all three of you had come at
me you might have been able to take them
well anyway it's over wait a minute you
set it up with three people but only two
bells if we worked together and got the
bells only two of us could keep them and
that would lead to group conflict and
the squad would break up exactly i
purposely pitted you against each other
huh i wanted to see if you could
overcome that and put the squad ahead of
yourselves a genine should have a
natural feel for teamwork but you it
never even crossed your mind sakura you
obsessed about Sasuke who was gone while
Naruto was right in front of you when
you wouldn't lift a finger to help him
naruto you do everything on your own
everything
and you Sasuke thought the others were
so far beneath you they were worthless
arrogance ninja missions are carried out
in squads of course you need individual
skills but teamwork is the most
essential element every Shinobi
understands this when individuals put
themselves above the squad this can lead
to failure and death for example Sakura
kill Naruto now or Sasuke dies
that's what happens on a mission
oh boy that was really scary
the enemy takes a hostage and you've got
an impossible choice and someone ends up
dead on every mission your life is on
the
line did you look at this stone the
names engraved on it
they are all ninja who are honored as
heroes in our village
that's it that's it that's it now I know
i've decided I'm going to have my name
engraved on that stone i'm not going to
live and die for nothing like a dog i'm
going to be a hero a hero
they are a special kind of hero huh what
kind of heroes are they come on tell us
well well they're all KIA ooh that
sounds real cool it means killed in
action they all died
[Music]
this is a memorial stone the names of my
closest friends are engraved
here oh
[Music]
all right I'm going to give you one more
chance but I'm going to make it much
harder on you you'll have 3 hours to get
a bell eat lunch now to build up
strength but Narut doesn't get
any it's your punishment for breaking
the rules and trying to eat by yourself
and if anyone tries to feed him that
person will immediately fail
i make the rules you follow them got
it i'm
leaving i listen to me huh
whether they pass or fail you must not
blame Kakashi
right
this is no big deal i can go without
eating for days for weeks believe it
this is no big deal
no problem
here
what no Sasuke you can't do that you
heard what the sensei said kakashi's
gone we need to get those bells as a
team if Naruto's hungry he'll be weak
and ineffective that hurts the team and
jeopardizes the mission
um
[Music]
Sasuke Sakura
okay thanks
don't thank me just hurry up and eat but
isn't that your lunch i'm on a diet i
mean I don't eat as much as Sasuke so
just take it Naruto i can't take it
because I can't move my hands you've got
to feed me hurry up he could come back
any minute
this is one time only that's it i'll
never do this again is that clear clear
the bells
Sakura uh
[Music]
You You broke the rules i hope you're
ready for the
[Music]
punishment any last words
but you said yes
you said that there were three of us
that's what you said and that's why suck
her up then we're all on this squad and
we're all in it together
yeah that's right we gave our lunch to
him because the three of us are one
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah believe it that's
right
the three of you are one that's your
excuse
[Music]
you pass huh huh
you pass
what do you mean how'd we pass you're
the first squad that ever succeeded the
others did exactly what I said and fell
into every trap they couldn't think for
themselves a ninja must see through
deception in the ninja world those who
break the rules are scum that's true but
those who abandon their friends are
worse than scum
[Music]
he's uh you know he's kind of cool
the exercise is over everyone passes
squad 7 starts its first mission
tomorrow
yes
i did it i did it believe it i'm a ninja
ninja ninja let's go home
[Music]
sure i did it
i knew they do this it happens every
time believe it
you guys forgot to untie
[Music]
me cultivate your hunger for you i
realize motivate us and make them more
realize climbing the mountain never
coming down breaking through the
contents never falling
[Music]
down my knees still shaken like I was
sneaking out the classroom by the back
door but I didn't care waiting is
wasting for people like me don't
try
[Applause]
[Music]
so cuz you wear
[Applause]
[Music]
hat don't try to look so wise don't cry
cuz you're so right
don't try with fakes or fears cuz you
will hate yourself in the end don't try
to live
[Music]
so it's all right don't try this
what's up with this all we're doing are
these boring training missions then
finally we get a chance at something big
and it turns out it's just guarding this
old man and he says I'm only a kid and
calls me a loser i won't tell you what I
call him back but I did tell him "Look
someday I'll be Hey are you listening to
me?" Next time a dangerous mission
journey to the land of waves don't miss
me as a full-on ninja